DC Showcase: Catwoman is a action, animation, crime
film directed by Lauren Montgomery.
Catwoman attempts to track down a mysterious cargo shipment that is
linked to a Gotham City crime boss called Rough Cut.
Catwoman / Selina Kyle (voice), played by Eliza Dushku.
Roughcut (voice), played by John DiMaggio.
Holly Robinson (voice), played by Liliana Mumy.
Moe (voice), played by Kevin Michael Richardson.
Buttermilk Skye (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Lily (voice), played by Cree Summer.
DC Showcase: Catwoman, also titled as simply Catwoman, is a 2011 short animated
superhero film, directed by Lauren Montgomery and written by Paul Dini.
It  was released on October 18, 2011, as a bonus feature and continuation of
the Catwoman story line on Batman: Year One Blu-ray and DVD.
It is the fifth installment in the DC Showcase series.
The film features Eliza Dushku as Catwoman / Selina Kyle in her first solo tale, as she attempts to bring both a Gotham City crime boss called
Rough Cut and his smuggling ring to an end, stumbling upon a mysterious cargo shipment far worse than just smuggled diamonds.
The film explores themes of superhero, cat burglar, diamond
theft, woman director, hand to hand combat.